wikinvest.com 2010-11-20

# Site:Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: April 13, 2010**

##  Introduction/Summary

Wikinvest ("we" or "us") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from you. Please read the following to understand our practices regarding personal information and how they affect you as you use our features and services. This statement discloses our current privacy practices; if we make material changes to these practices, we will post them here, via prominent notice on our homepage, or by email. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us at [privacy@wikinvest.com](mailto:privacy@wikinvest.com "mailto:privacy@wikinvest.com"). 

Wikinvest is certified through the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. In order to obtain certification, Wikinvest disclosed its information privacy practices to TRUSTe to ensure compliance with TRUSTe’s requirements. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [privacy@wikinvest.com](mailto:privacy@wikinvest.com "mailto:privacy@wikinvest.com"). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry, or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should [contact TRUSTe](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url "http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url"). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

##  Information Collected by Us

We collect user submitted account information such as name, email address, and profile photo to identify you and send you notifications related to the use of the service. We maintain information you submit in your profile on the site, and we also collect user submitted content about companies and investing and other information. We collect information from you when you send us feedback as well. Some information collected is not explicitly submitted by the user. Examples of such information include (but are not limited to): browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp. See “Use of Cookies and IP Address” below. 

##  Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time, Wikinvest may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If you participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to better monitor site traffic for the improvement of the site and categorization of our users for advertisers. 

##  Blogs, Forums, and Wikis

If you use a blog, forum, wiki, or other publicly published content product on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

##  Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews

From time to time, we post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site, which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. 

##  How We Use Your Information

Information such as your full name, profile photo and any personally identifiable information you have included in your profile may be shown to users, primarily in conjunction with articles you have contributed to. We use information supplied to us to respond to your feedback or inquiries. In addition, part of the service is a real time feed that displays user activity. For example, if you post an article - a streaming notice will be posted about that activity or the activity of other users. This is part of the service and you may not opt-out of this functionality. Your full name and email address may also be used when you send an email notification to another user on our site. We may also use your email address to send you communications from us or messages that we send you on behalf of other users, but you may opt out of receiving emails by changing your email preferences in your profile settings. 

##  Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, timestamp data, and other information help us diagnose problems with our server, administer Wikinvest, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this non-personally identifiable information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site. 

##  Updating/Accessing Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete/remove it by making the change on your profile page or by emailing our Customer Support team at [feedback@wikinvest.com](mailto:feedback@wikinvest.com "mailto:feedback@wikinvest.com"). We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. 

##  Use of Cookies and IP Addresses

Like most websites, Wikinvest requires cookies to function properly. Cookies are small text files that reside on a user's computer and identify you as a unique user. We use cookies to refine our site and simplify the user experience. For example, the use of cookies allows registered users to enter our site without explicitly typing in their email address and password every time, and it allows us to personalize your experience on the site by suggesting articles you may be interested in. For these reasons we do tie personally identifiable information such as our email address to our cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Wikinvest site. We use a tracking utility company that uses cookies and Web beacons on our site. We have no access or control of these third party tracking utilities. 

##  Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf "http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf"). 

##  Transfer/Disclosure of Information

Most of the information you provide on our site is publicly exposed. However, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information. We do not share your personal information for a third parties’ promotional use. We will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. Further, we may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Wikinvest, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing. 

##  Security

Your Wikinvest account is password-protected. We try very hard to protect our users' information. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

_You hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner._

##  Email/Direct Mail and Opt-out

Registered members can opt-out of personal messages initiated by users and/or opt-out of receiving notifications initiated by us by going to the preferences section of the Profile area of the Web site. Unregistered and Registered users that do not wish to receive emails may opt-out of receiving any communications by following the instructions contained in all emails. 

##  Controlling Your Personal Information

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) via reviews, messages, forums, postings, or in other areas of the Wikinvest site, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Wikinvest. Please do not post any personal information on the Wikinvest site or in other areas that you expect to keep private. 

As a registered Wikinvest user, you can modify your personal information at any time by accessing your profile by clicking on your username in the account section of the shelf. 

##  Respecting Children’s Privacy

This website is not directed to children, and we do not knowingly solicit information from any child under the age of 13. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us we will delete it as soon as possible. 

##  Links

Our website may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. We do not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy polices on these third party websites. 

##  Frames

The Web site utilizes framing techniques to make it appear that the user is still on the site when the user is actually on a third party Web site. We do this so that you will have a more seamless experience on the site. The privacy policy of the site that governs any collection of data will appear on those pages. 

##  Modification to the Privacy Policy

By using the website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the site. We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If a material change is made to this Privacy Policy and/or the way we use our users’ personally identifiable information, then we will post a prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

##  Contact

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy or any other privacy or security concern, please send an e-mail to [privacy@wikinvest.com](mailto:privacy@wikinvest.com "mailto:privacy@wikinvest.com"). 

     Wikinvest
     1085 Mission St. 
     San Francisco, CA 94103
     Phone: 415.558.9611

**Wikinvest © 2006, 2007, 2008, 2009, 2010.** Use of this site is subject to express Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, and Disclaimer. By continuing past this page, you agree to abide by these terms. Any information provided by Wikinvest, including but not limited to company data, competitors, business analysis, market share, sales revenues and other operating metrics, earnings call analysis, conference call transcripts, industry information, or price targets should not be construed as research, trading tips or recommendations, or investment advice and is provided with no warrants as to its accuracy. Stock market data, including US and International equity symbols, stock quotes, share prices, earnings ratios, and other fundamental data is provided by data partners. Stock market quotes delayed at least 15 minutes for NASDAQ, 20 mins for NYSE and AMEX. Market data by [Xignite](http://www.xignite.com/). See data providers for more details. Company names, products, services and branding cited herein may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. The use of trademarks or service marks of another is not a representation that the other is affiliated with, sponsors, is sponsored by, endorses, or is endorsed by Wikinvest.
